euroweeklynews.com 2011-01-10

# Euro Weekly News | Privacy Policy | The Largest English Language Newspapers in Spain

Wednesday, 02 June 2010 17:31 

Introduction

Euro Weekly News Media Group respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. We have, therefore, established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Euro Weekly News Media Group's web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

Euro Weekly News Media Group strives to comply with all applicable laws worldwide that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Euro Weekly News Media Group intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an “adequate” level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our aim is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.

Information We Collect

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and/or a set of numbers, that serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any web page within Euro Weekly News Media Group, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and/or IP address. The domain name and/or IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of Euro Weekly News Media Group, its users, or to cooperate with various law enforcement agencies. See also “Disclosure to Third Parties” below. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals.

Euro Weekly News Media Group may offer access to services that require registration. In that event, your registration and/or contact information may be used to send notification to you of Euro Weekly News Media Group products and/or services by e-mail. We maintain a strict “No-Spam” policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

When you use co-branded services or those provided by a third party within Euro Weekly News Media Group, your Personal Information may be passed to that third party provider. Its use of your Personal Information is subject to their applicable privacy policies.

Information We Do Not Collect

When you visit our site, we do not collect your name, email address or any other Personal Information unless you provide it to us.

Security

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within Euro Weekly News Media Group or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

Third Parties

Some pages on the Euro Weekly News Media Group web site include links to third party web sites. These sites are governed by their own privacy statements, and Euro Weekly News Media Group is not responsible for their operations, including but not limited to their information practices. Users submitting information to or through third party web sites should review the privacy statement of those sites before providing them with Personal Information.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose Personal Information online (e.g., through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere) that information can be collected and used by others.

Disclosures to Third Parties

Euro Weekly News Media Group will disclose Personal Information and/or an IP address when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

1: Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Euro Weekly News Media Group.

2: Protect and defend the rights or property of Euro Weekly News Media Group and related properties, or visitors to Euro Weekly News Media Group and related properties.

3: Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Euro Weekly News Media Group legal notice, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing Euro Weekly News Media Group or its related properties.

4: Fulfill a user’s order or request.

Euro Weekly News Media Group  uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Euro Weekly News Media Group reserves the right to transfer all such information in connection with the sale of all or part of Euro Weekly News Media Group capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

Your Consent to this Agreement

By using Euro Weekly News Media Group’s website(s), you consent to the collection and use of information by Euro Weekly News Media Group as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Introduction**

Euro Weekly News Media Group respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. We have, therefore, established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Euro Weekly News Media Group's web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.  
Euro Weekly News Media Group strives to comply with all applicable laws worldwide that are designed to protect your privacy.

Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Euro Weekly News Media Group intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an “adequate” level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our aim is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.

**Information We Collect**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and/or a set of numbers, that serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any web page within Euro Weekly News Media Group, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and/or IP address. The domain name and/or IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of Euro Weekly News Media Group, its users, or to cooperate with various law enforcement agencies. See also “Disclosure to Third Parties” below. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals.

Euro Weekly News Media Group may offer access to services that require registration. In that event, your registration and/or contact information may be used to send notification to you of Euro Weekly News Media Group products and/or services by e-mail. We maintain a strict “No-Spam” policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

When you use co-branded services or those provided by a third party within Euro Weekly News Media Group, your Personal Information may be passed to that third party provider. Its use of your Personal Information is subject to their applicable privacy policies.

**Information We Do Not Collect**

When you visit our site, we do not collect your name, email address or any other Personal Information unless you provide it to us.

**Security**

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within Euro Weekly News Media Group or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

**Third Parties**

** ** Some pages on the Euro Weekly News Media Group web site include links to third party web sites. These sites are governed by their own privacy statements, and Euro Weekly News Media Group is not responsible for their operations, including but not limited to their information practices. Users submitting information to or through third party web sites should review the privacy statement of those sites before providing them with Personal Information.Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose Personal Information online (e.g., through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere) that information can be collected and used by others.

**Disclosures to Third Parties**

** ** Euro Weekly News Media Group will disclose Personal Information and/or an IP address when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

1: Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Euro Weekly News Media Group.

2: Protect and defend the rights or property of Euro Weekly News Media Group and related properties, or visitors to Euro Weekly News Media Group and related properties.

3: Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Euro Weekly News Media Group legal notice, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing Euro Weekly News Media Group or its related properties.

4: Fulfill a user’s order or request. Euro Weekly News Media Group uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure.

Euro Weekly News Media Group reserves the right to transfer all such information in connection with the sale of all or part of Euro Weekly News Media Group capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information.

We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

**Google Analytics**

** ** This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

**Your Consent to this Agreement**

** ** By using Euro Weekly News Media Group’s website(s), you consent to the collection and use of information by Euro Weekly News Media Group as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
